[
  {
    "deckName": "Deck3",
    "labelDescription": "A1 Level",
    "cards": {
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "sas",
          "answer": "ss",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 15, 2024, 9:11:28 AM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "sleep",
          "answer": "ngủ",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 16, 2024, 9:11:24 AM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 11
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "eat",
          "answer": "ăn",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 16, 2024, 9:11:29 AM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 12
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "go",
          "answer": "di",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 16, 2024, 9:11:33 AM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 13
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 0,
    "dueCards": 4,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [
        {
          "date": "Thursday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Wednesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ],
      "statisticsInMonth": [
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 8,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Deck1",
    "cards": {
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "hello",
          "answer": "chào",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:33:54 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 4
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "123567891",
          "answer": "2345689122",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:33:56 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 5
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "bye",
          "answer": "tạm biệt",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:33:56 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 5
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "study",
          "answer": "học",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:33:55 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 5
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 0,
    "dueCards": 4,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [
        {
          "date": "Wednesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ],
      "statisticsInMonth": [
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 4,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 1
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 1
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 4
        }
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Deck2",
    "labelDescription": "A1 level",
    "cards": {
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "sleep",
          "answer": "ngủ",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:38:59 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 6
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "eat",
          "answer": "ăn",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 15, 2024, 9:39:01 PM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 7
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 0,
    "dueCards": 2,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [
        {
          "date": "Wednesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 2
        }
      ],
      "statisticsInMonth": [
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 1,
          "dueCards": 1
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 4
        }
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Deck11",
    "labelDescription": "",
    "cards": {
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "confidential",
          "answer": "Bí mật",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:59:24 PM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 1
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "bread",
          "answer": "bánh mì",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 14, 2024, 9:59:23 PM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 1
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 0,
    "dueCards": 2,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [
        {
          "date": "Thursday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Wednesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ],
      "statisticsInMonth": [
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 2,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 2,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ]
    }
  },
  {
    "deckName": "toeic",
    "labelDescription": "",
    "cards": {
      "cards": []
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 0,
    "dueCards": 0,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [],
      "statisticsInMonth": []
    }
  },
  {
    "deckName": "toeic",
    "labelDescription": "",
    "cards": {
      "cards": []
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 0,
    "dueCards": 0,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [],
      "statisticsInMonth": []
    }
  },
  {
    "deckName": "Vocabulary Review",
    "labelDescription": "Test App",
    "cards": {
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "programme",
          "answer": "chương trình",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 20, 2024, 3:17:56 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 2
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "computer",
          "answer": "máy tính",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 20, 2024, 3:17:53 PM",
            "answerType": "MEDIUM",
            "cycle": 2
          }
        },
        {
          "question": "study",
          "answer": "học",
          "selector": {
            "deadlineAt": "Jun 21, 2024, 3:17:49 PM",
            "answerType": "CORRECT",
            "cycle": 2
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "newCards": 0,
    "learnedCards": 3,
    "dueCards": 0,
    "easyCard": 3,
    "mediumCard": 2,
    "hardCard": 1,
    "StatOfDeck": {
      "statisticsInWeek": [
        {
          "date": "Tuesday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "Thursday",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ],
      "statisticsInMonth": [
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 3
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 0,
          "learnedCards": 3,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 3,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 0
        },
        {
          "date": "June",
          "newCards": 3,
          "learnedCards": 0,
          "dueCards": 0
        }
      ]
    }
  }
]